Open your lips, and ask for the mercy of God for yourself.
You need the mercy of God to speak for you.
His mercy is enough.
His favour.
Mercy, mercy, mercy.
Prayer!
Viewers at home, ask for the mercy of God, the favour of God.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In Jesus Chist' name we pray.
When you take note of people
before you in your family,
you will notice that they had been aspiring for certain positions.
But they could not get it.
This shows that there is a limitation in the family.
Not only you, but people before you.
It has been their desire to get to certain positions;
it has been very difficult.
No way because there is a limitation in the family that needs to be broken.
As for me, each time I sit down, I say, "Wow!"
What a grace God has given to me to break this limitation.
You - you need to break your own.
I smile; I say I have broken this limitation.
The cycle of limitation.
We are not only talking of position this time;
we are talking about position and peace.
Position needs peace; position needs comfort.
Position minus peace is not position.
You need peace and comfort.
Open your lips and begin to break that cycle of life; that limitation in the family - break it!
I will join you in faith to break that limitation.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus!
Cycle of limitation - be broken.
Right now, begin to release yourself!
Release your family from that sickness!
From disease, from limitation.
Begin to release your family.
Release your family.
I release my family.
I release myself.
I release!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Overflow Congregation
In the mighty name of Jesus!
Yes, we are moving forward.
Many of us, we do not know how to pray.
When you ask God for bread. Immediately you say, "God, give me bread".
Immediately say, "Thank You for giving me bread".
Then you come back again - "Give me bread, give me bread.
Thank You for giving me bread.
Give me bread...give me bread...give me bread.
Thank You for giving me bread. Thank You for giving me bread".
These two things must go together. Ask and Thank You.
But you will not say, "Thank You", because you want to receive before you say thank you.
This has been robbing you of your blessings.
"Heal me, Lord. Heal me, Lord. Thank You for healing me."
"Deliver me, Lord. Deliver me, Lord.
Thank You for delivering me."
That is how to pray.
Thanks must follow your request.
Pari passu.
Synonymous.
Not: "Heal me...heal me...heal me".
You won't say thank you until the pain disappears.
He is the Healer.
He can heal you. Even if He has not healed you. He can heal you.
He is what He says He is. He is the Healer.
Even if He doesn't heal you.
He is the Deliverer. Even if He doesn't delivered you.
You have to give thanks to Him for those He has delivered,
and He has delivered you before - give thanks to Him.
Even if He has not delivered you now, give thanks to Him for delivering some people now.
Look at the sister that just shared her testimony. Thanks must go along with your prayer.
Are you ready with me?
You want to release yourself and your community from this yoke.
Now we are here today to get it done,
and to release your family from the cage.
Now open your lips, and release yourself and your family from the cage
Prayer!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Right now open your lips, and begin to thank Jesus for releasing your family.
For releasing you and releasing the community.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Right now open your lips again.
Begin to release your community and yourself from the cycle of limitation.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Cycle of limitation.
Certain position.
You deserve excellence.
Yes! Where is excellence in your health?
Where is excellence in time of peace?
Where is excellence in time of comfort?
Where is excellence in time of position?
There is limitation that needs to be broken by God's intervention through you.
Right now open you lips.
Begin to release yourself and your community from that sickness and disease,
from that cycle of limitation,
that limitation in progress.
Release yourself.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Begin to rewrite the history.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Give thanks to God for releasing yours.
Overflow Congregation
Viewers at home, begin to give thanks to God for releasing you.
For giving you the grace to rewrite the history of sickness to good health.
History of hardship to blessing.
History of hardship to breakthrough.
History of limitation in progress to progress.
Begin to rewrite it, rewrite the history.
Give thanks to God for giving you the grace to rewrite the history.
From sickness to good health.
From hardship to breakthrough.
History of limitation to progress.
History of yoke, cycle of limitation, to deliverance of the family and yourself.
Rewrite it, rewrite the history.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Give thanks to God. Give thanks to Him.
Hallelujah.
Give thanks to God.
Thank You, Lord. In Jesus Christ' name.
Let the people of God of say, Amen.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations and Changing the world.